https://www.lobstersports.com/privacy-policy/

Lobster Sports mobile app privacy policy
Lobster Sports respects your privacy and does not collect nor store your personal information.
Neither our mobile apps nor our machines connect back to Lobster Sports. Anything that happens on your phone stays on your phone. On our grand series machines which have the ability to customize drills, any drill data is stored only on the machine.
Lobster Sports website privacy policy
Your privacy is very important to Lobster Sports. This privacy policy describes the information we gather about you and the purpose for which it is used.
You may interact with Lobster Sports in one of three ways: contacting us by email, contacting us by phone, or by placing an order on our website. The kinds of personal information that we may collect during these interactions include: name, address, email address, telephone number, and credit card information.
We also log certain non-personal information when you visit our website, such as the type of browser used, the type of operating system used, and the domain of your Internet service provider. We log this information using 'cookies,' which are small data text files that Web sites store on your computer's hard drive if your Web browser permits. Cookies, which can later be retrieved to identify you to Lobster Sports, make your use of our site easier, allow you to retrieve earlier shopping carts, and help us to maintain a secure site. For your safety, you will be unable to shop on our site if your browser is not set to accept cookies.
We use the non-personal information we collect to analyze the overall traffic on our site. This analysis helps us make site design changes to improve your experience.
We may disclose the personal information you provide as required by a particular legal process (e.g., court order, subpoena, law enforcement agency's request).
Lobster Sports uses several of the latest encryption technologies to keep your personal information safe. Your private ordering information - including your credit card number - is encrypted using several keys for maximum security. Your credit card and billing information cannot be poached as it travels through our secure ordering system (128-bit SSL encryption), and the numbers are unreadable to anyone trying to access the site remotely. We have implemented the requisite physical, electronic, and managerial processes to prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security.
You may contact us at any time to update the information we have about you. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either by email, postal mail, or phone, please let us know by sending us an email or by contacting us.
Please note that such requests may take up to 6-8 weeks to become effective. Please also note that when you make a purchase, we will send you emails to confirm your order and may also need to contact you by phone, mail, or email if we have other questions regarding your order.
Products
Battery Ball Machines
Electric Ball Machines
Pickleball Machines
Accessories
Court Equipment
Parts
Support
Company:
Phone:*
E-mail:*
Comments or Questions:
Forgot your password?
Telephone:
Enter Your Email Address:
Close
